{
    "subject": "Palito_Ortega",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "El_T\u00edo_Disparate",
    "human_readable": "Palito Ortega acted in the movie El T\u00edo Disparate.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9853679537773132,
            "question": "What role did Palito Ortega play in El T\u00edo Disparate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9109596014022827,
            "question": "Who acted in the movie El T\u00edo Disparate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8407359719276428,
            "question": "Who else acted in the movie El T\u00edo Disparate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8177391886711121,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie Palito Ortega starred in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8052292466163635,
            "question": "Is Palito Ortega known for acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6332976818084717,
            "question": "Is El T\u00edo Disparate a popular movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5686575770378113,
            "question": "What genre is the movie El T\u00edo Disparate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5521164536476135,
            "question": "When was the movie El T\u00edo Disparate released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5430231690406799,
            "question": "Are there any other famous movies featuring Palito Ortega?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.542849600315094,
            "question": "What is Palito Ortega's nationality?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Palito Ortega acted in the movie El T\u00edo Disparate.",
            "html": "yago_6556_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other famous movies featuring Palito Ortega?",
            "html": "yago_6556_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the movie El T\u00edo Disparate released?",
            "html": "yago_6556_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the movie El T\u00edo Disparate?",
            "html": "yago_6556_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6556_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6556_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6556_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6556_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6556_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6556_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6556_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6556_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6556_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6556_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation: The text does not mention a specific movie called \"El T\u00edo Disparate\" where Palito Ortega acted, except for one document (path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_6556/re-ranker-msmarco/12.txt) that only mentions the title of the movie without providing any information about the actors."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents mentions that Palito Ortega has appeared in multiple films, including one titled \"El t\u00edo Disparate\" (1978), which is consistent with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}